Guide to the Ramón Hernández Tejano Music Collection
The Wittliff Collections
- Costumes
  Costumes are arranged alphabetically by artist. Many of the costumes were worn on stage and range from the highly elaborate and detailed to a more Western-influenced style. Some of the many highlights are an intricately beaded dress worn by Rosita Fernandez, multiple custom-made jumpsuits worn by Little Joe Hernandez, a multicolored sequined jacket with pink satin pants worn by Jamie De Anda, a faux leather jacket emblazoned with "Rockstar Angel" worn by Shelley Lares, and a pink Western-style button-down shirt with red acid-washed jeans worn by Emilio Navaira. There is also a small number of T-shirts worn by artists, some with political or activist messages.
  The subseries of costume accessories is further separated into hats, shoes, and miscellaneous accessories, including Freddie Martinez's ties, Emilio Navaira's belt with a belt buckle, Oscar Martinez's sunglasses, and Steve Jordan's eyepatch.
  - Shirt worn by artists
    - Little Joe Hernandez. Clinton/Gore Inauguration Sweatshirt, 1992 (Box 223)
    - Little Joe Hernandez. Ignite the Vote T-shirt, undated (Box 223)
    - Little Joe Hernandez. Cartoon chicken T-shirt, undated (Box 223)
    - Sunny Ozuna. Tejanos for Hunger T-shirt, undated (Box 223)
    - Patsy Torres. Cartoon cats T-shirt, undated (Box 223)
  - Costume Accessories
    - Shoes
      - Carlos Guzman - Black striped oxfords, undated (Box 224)
      - Roy Montelongo - White suede loafers, undated (Box 225)
      - Cino Moreno (The Latinaires) - White low top shoes, undated (Box 226)
      - Sunny Ozuna - Multicolored felt oxfords, undated (Box 227)
      - Ruben Ramos - Black and white oxfords, undated (Box 228)
      - Rene Rene - Tan loafers, undated (Box 229)
      - Rene Rene - Tan loafers, undated (Box 230)
    - Cowboy Boots
      - Little Joe Hernandez - Tan cowboy boots, undated (Box 231)
      - Emilio Navaira - Gray and tan cowboy boots, undated (Box 232)
      - Marcos Orozco - Black cowboy boots with red and white stitching, undated (Box 233)
      - Janie C. Ramirez - Brown cowboy boots, undated (Box 234)
    - Hats
      - Randy Garibay: Gray Stensonian cowboy hat (signed), undated (Box 235)
      - David Lee Garza - Straw cowboy hat, undated (Box 236)
      - Arturo "Sauce" Gonzales - Brown Dobbs, undated (Box 237)
      - Little Joe Hernandez - Black cowboy hat with "Teach the Children" pin, undated (Box 238)
      - Little Joe Hernandez - Baseball caps (2), 1993, undated (Box 239)
      - Shelly Lares - Straw cowboy hat, undated (Box 240)
      - Valerio Longoria - Straw Sombreros Paygo, undated (Box 241)
      - Isidro "El Indio" Lopez - Feathered headdress, undated (Box 242)
      - Narciso Martinez - Brown Dobbs, undated (Box 243)
      - Raulito Navaira - Tan Stetson, undated (Box 244)
      - Joe Posada - Black Stetson, undated (Box 245)
      - Rene Rene - White Rocawear fedora, undated (Box 246)
      - Mingo Saldivar - Black cowboy hat, undated (Box 247)
      - Juan Viesca - Tan cowboy hat, undated (Box 248)
    - Accessories
      - Steve Jordan - Leather Eyepatch, undated (Box 249, Item 1)
      - Emilio Navaira - Black leather belt with silver details and tan stitching and silver and gold belt buckle with a gold bull rider, undated (Box 249, Item 2)
      - Freddie Martinez - Maroon silk tie with trumpets; Black silk tie with music notes and trumpets, undated (Box 249, Item 3)
      - Oscar Martinez - Sunglasses, undated (Box 249, Item 4)
    - Suitcases
      - Freddy Fender - Miller Lite garment bag, undated (Box 250)
  - Costumes
    - Sonny Ace - White button-down shirt with musical notes down front, undated (Item 001)
    - Joe Bravo - Grey tuxedo suit jacket; grey button-down shirt with ruffled front, undated (Item 002)
    - Laura Canales - Black satin shirt with pink flowers; black satin shorts, undated (Item 003)
    - Laura Canales - Red blouse and matching skirt, undated (Item 004)
    - Julio Casas - Burgundy bolero jacket with horseshoe pattern; matching pants, undated (Item 005)
    - Julio Casas - Orange blazer, undated (Item 006)
    - Jaime De Anda (y los Chamacos) - Multi-colored sequined suit jacket; pink satin pants with sequins, undated (Item 007)
    - El Desperado - Black satin baseball jacket, "El Desperado" on back, undated (Item 008)
    - Albert "Tiger" Diaz (La Sombra) - Black faux-leather jacket with silver design on arms and collar; matching pants with "Tiger" on the leg, undated (Item 009)
    - Los Dinos - Black vest with clear rhinestones, undated (Item 010)
    - Freddy Fender - Blue suit jacket with sequins; matching bell bottom pants; blue ruffle front shirt, undated (Item 011)
    - Freddy Fender - Miller Brewing Company leather and felt bomber jacket with "Portraits of Success Hispanics in the World of Music" / "Retrat Exitos Hispanoamericanos En El Mundo de Musica" patch on back, undated (Item 012)
    - Rosita Fernandez - Black Spanish-styled skirt with lace trim and tulle, undated (Item 013)
    - Rosita Fernandez - Red dress with green sequins and intricate beadwork showing village scene and cacti, black lace and tulle; White silk scarf, undated (Item 013a)
    - Oscar G.- Black satin baseball jacket, "Oscar G. El Grupo Sol" embroidered on front and back, undated (Item 014)
    - David Lee Garza - Denim and canvas button-down shirt, "Los Musicales" and Coors Light logo, undated (Item 015)
    - Arturo "Sauce" Gonzalez - White leather zippered vest, with piano design on back, signed by Gonzalez on back, undated (Item 016)
    - Carlos Guzman - Black and white checkered double-breasted suit jacket; matching pants; black satin button-down shirt; black and white tie, undated (Item 017)
    - Emma Hernández - White dress with gold glitter, undated (Item 018)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Black vest with leather trim, undated (Item 019)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Black suit jacket; tuxedo pants, undated (Item 020)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Black satin baseball jacket, "Little Joe" on back, undated (Item 021)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Black shirt with bib front; blue jeans with chains with rooster details, undated (Item 022)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Multi-colored, striped Mexican blanket-style suit jacket; matching cummerbund and bow tie, undated (Item 023)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Cream jumpsuit with "L.J." monogram, musical notes, and flowers on front, undated (Item 024)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Gold satin jumpsuit with gold sequins on collar, pockets, and belt, undated (Item 025)
    - Little Joe Hernandez - Rose colored velour jumpsuit with "L.J." monogram, undated (Item 026)
    - Ram Herrera - White bolero jacket with roses on front (signed by Herrera on inside right arm); matching white pants and vest; red cotton button-down shirt, undated (Item 027)
    - Ram Herrera (Montana Band) - Grey bolero jacket with silver sequins; black tuxedo pants with silver sequin stripe, undated (Item 028)
    - Flaco Jimenez - Blue Southwestern button-down shirt, undated (Item 029)
    - Johnneil - Red polo shirt, "Johnneil" embroidered on front; "La Raza" on back, undated (Item 030)
    - Shelly Lares - Black faux-leather zippered jacket with metal studs on collar and trim and "Rockstar Angel" in glitter on back, undated (Item 031)
    - Little Pete and the Miracles - Green and pink checked short-sleeved shirt; green pants, undated (Item 032)
    - Little Pete and the Miracles - Blue, green, and white button-down short-sleeved shirt with white knit waistband, undated (Item 033)
    - Little Pete and the Miracles - Orange, yellow, and white button-down short- sleeved shirt with yellow knit waistband, undated (Item 034)
    - Little Pete and the Miracles - Blue bolero jacket with flower texture, undated (Item 035)
    - Little Pete and the Miracles - Pink bolero jacket with flower texture, undated (Item 036)
    - Beatriz Llamas - White knit dress with stripes and red top, undated (Item 037)
    - Beatriz Llamas - White shirt with embroidery, undated (Item 038)
    - Isidro Lopez - White button-down shirt with musical notes on collar and cuffs; red tie with keyboard and saxophone, undated (Item 039)
    - Isidro Lopez - White vest with sequined "El Indio" on front and "Isidro Lopez" on back with a sequined image of a Native American man, undated (Item 040)
    - David Marez - White sequined suit jacket, undated (Item 041)
    - David Marez - Red satin baseball jacket with "Albert Esquivel" embroidered on front; "David Marez and People" on back, undated (Item 042)
    - Freddie Martinez - Black suit jacket, burgundy and black button-down shirt; red tie, undated (Item 043)
    - Oscar Martinez - Blue sequined suit jacket with yellow rose in lapel; red satin bow tie; one multi-colored ruffled sleeve, undated (Item 044)
    - Sonny Melendrez - Blue satin baseball jacket with "Ramon" embroidered on chest and logo for "Sonny Melendrez Comedy and Music Show" on back, undated (Item 045)
    - Lydia Mendoza - Purple dress with sequin patterns and tulle, undated (Item 046)
    - Augie Meyers - Black leather vest, undated (Item 047)
    - Michelle - Black and pink sequined dress, undated (Item 048)
    - Carlos Miranda - Black bolero jacket with gold trim on pockets and cuffs, undated (Item 049)
    - Emilio Navaira - Pink striped button-down shirt; red acid wash jeans, undated (Item 050)
    - Raulito Navaira - Blue short-sleeved button down, "World Car" logo, undated (Item 051)
    - Sunny Ozuna - Peach tuxedo suit jacket, vest, shirt with ruffled collar, and pants with a sequin stripe, undated (Item 052)
    - Sunny Ozuna - Purple, green & gold velour suit jacket; lavender cummerbund, undated (Item 053)
    - Sunny Ozuna - Lavender bolero jacket with purple velour trim; vest; matching pants; purple velour cummerbund, undated (Item 054)
    - Joe Posada - Black subtle pinstripe suit jacket and pants, undated (Item 055)
    - Augustin Ramirez - Faux-leopard fur vest; gold chains, undated (Item 056)
    - Alfonso Ramos - White suit jacket with small gold-sequined squares; matching pants, undated (Item 057)
    - Ruben Ramos - Gold sequined suit jacket, undated (Item 058)
    - René René - Yellow suit jacket, matching pants; black button-down shirt; yellow tie, undated (Item 059)
    - Elida Reyna (y Avante) - Black leather vest with fringe and beads, undated (Item 060)
    - Joe Rios - Black satin baseball jacket, "Joe" embroidered on front; "Montana Band" on back (partial lettering missing), undated (Item 061)
    - Henry Rivas - Grey suit jacket; card with photo of Rivas in front pocket, undated (Item 062)
    - Blanca Rodriguez - Black dress with white lace trim and multi-colored flower embroidery, undated (Item 063)
    - Gilbert Rodriguez - Burnt orange suit jacket, matching pants, and vest, undated (Item 064)
    - Placido Salazar - Orange suede jacket, undated (Item 065)
    - Michael Salgado - Black acid-wash snap-down shirt, undated (Item 066)
    - Jessy Serrata - Maroon blazer with matching pants, undated (Item 067)
    - Rene Serrata - Ivory button-down-down shirt with blue western trim on front and back yoke, undated (Item 068)
    - Rudy Tee (Reno Bops) - Multi-colored suit jacket with black collar, undated (Item 069)
    - Patsy Torres - Camouflage one-armed shirt; olive pants, undated (Item 070)
    - Verónique - White cotton t-shirt; green satin skirt with multi-colored tulle, decorative green satin band, undated (Item 071)
    - Rita Vidaurri - Black short sleeved Mexican-style dress with turquoise embroidery, undated (Item 072)
    - Juan Viesca - Cream Western-style button down shirt with brown yoke and cuffs; black pants (shirt signed and dated 1950), undated (Item 073)
    - Unidentified - Texas flag vest, undated (Item 074)
- Artifacts and Framed Material
  Series XII: Artifacts and Framed Material, 1983-1997, undated
  Arranged alphabetically by artist. The artifacts include Hugo Guerrero's accordion and instrument cases and a public address speaker signed by Michael Salgado and Isidro "El Indio" Lopez, respectively. There is also a life-size cardboard cut-out Coca-Cola advertisement featuring Selena and two cardboard movie posters for the Selena film.
  Framed material includes paintings, photographs, and posters. Rosita Fernandez is particularly well-represented with a portrait painted by Frank Puente Harris, an illustrated song dedicated to her by David Kresh, and an event poster for her 60th Anniversary at La Villita Assembly Hall. There are also posters of Freddie Martinez and Selena. As well as a framed copy of Siempre Tu Eres CD by Jackie y Los Romanticos. It is also arranged alphabetically by artist.
  - Framed Items
    - Rosita Fernandez - Painting by Frank Puente, 1983 (Item 075)
    - Rosita Fernandez - Rosita's 60th Anniversary at La Villita Assembly Hall poster, 1990 (Item 076)
    - Rosita Fernandez - Illustrated song by David Kresh, undated (Item 077)
    - Jackie y Romantico. Siempre Tu Eres CD (with album cover and credits), 1997 (Item 078)
    - Freddie Martinez. Poster with gold frame, undated (Item 079)
    - Selena. Poster, undated (Item 080)
  - Artifacts
    - Hugo Guerrero (Fandango) - Galanti accordion in case, undated (Item 081)
    - Isidro "El Indio" Lopez - Public address speaker (signed), undated (Item 082)
    - Michael Salgado - Lid of equipment case (signed), undated (Item 083)
  - Cardboard cutouts and posters
    - Selena cardboard cutout for Coke, undated (Item 084)
    - Selena film cardboard cutout, undated (Item 085)
    - Selena film stand-up cardboard poster, undated (Item 086)